6:18 richard southern joins us now
richard Manulife is cutting hundreds of
jobs and then replacing them with
machines it's the way goes these days
isn't it Francis rides the machines that
Manulife 700 jobs being cut at the
insurer that's the announcement we got
in today and that's 5.3 percent of
manualized canadian workforce the
insurer says it's part of a plan to
digitize its operations says the cuts
will come through voluntary exit and
attrition this is really what we see
especially in the financial industry
right now we're seeing big profits from
the insurers and from the banks but
we're also seeing them turning to
technologies like AI to streamline their
operations we're also seeing customers
go and do their banking in their
insurance operations more online so
that's why job cuts are happening it's
the rise of the machines Francis now the
largest condo available in Toronto has
been sold to a cryptocurrency Baron yeah
this is the top of the former Trump
Tower building downtown Francis Anthony
delaurio the co-founder of aetherium
that digital currency he has bought this
now for 28 million laps yeah it was been
sitting empty for years nobody bought it
of course the building now owned by
invest hotels they call it the Adelaide
hotel it's going to be rebranded the st.
Regis in a little bit bloomberg news
reports the delaurio spent 28 million on
this and how did he financed it he
didn't take out a mortgage Frances he
cashed in some of his digital currency
and wire transferred the money that's
that didn't even think twice about it
the condo fees by the way almost fifteen
thousand dollars a month this is I guess
the only way you're doing something like
that these days is to make billions in
cryptocurrency like this gentleman has
it's not the most expensive condo ever
sold one went for 40 million out in
Vancouver hmm interesting know that he
wants to put it into bricks and mortar
though right it's true and he said this
he said this is my sort of fallback plan
to get into to real estate which
obviously he views as being a bit more
secure than digital currency absolutely
although at the top of that building I
don't know WestJet's new budget airline
took flight yesterday so today though
there's news that a European budget
carrier is about to enter Canada
yeah it's Norwegian and we're getting
some more news on this this these guys
are big as you know France is in Europe
kind of
ultra low-cost carrier they're Norwegian
coming to Canada now they're gonna fly
out of Hamilton and Montreal and they're
gonna go to Europe but they're also
gonna go to the Caribbean because
they're a European airline they're
allowed to fly to European islands in
the Caribbean out of Canada so a one-way
flight between Hamilton and the Dublin
Ireland going for about two hundred and
seventy nine dollars when they start up
in the fall so we start to see a lot of
competition and we'll see if that's
gonna bring prices down even more in the
next couple of my interesting with the
European Caribbean loophole there it is
you know go into something like
Martinique and some of these European
islands but again you got to go to
Hamilton first for swoop and for
Norwegian and that's good I think put a
lot of people here in the GTA off don't
you think though if it's gonna save you
a buck you never know yeah yeah Burger
King apologized for offensive worldcup
related ads in Russia well this was a
this was a wild one up Burger King
offered free whoppers and cash to any
Russian woman who got pregnant by a
world without player oh yeah at first
the company said it was socially
responsible of them as the women would
obtain the best football genes and
ensure the Russian team for generations
oh boy
Burger King quickly apologized pulled
the ads said it wouldn't happen again
fact of the matter though is ads in
Russia often play on sexist stereotypes
especially ads around sporting events
women's rights activists in the country
increasingly speaking out against them
so Burger King quickly trying to correct
their mistake on that one yikes
well it is the first day of summer
Richard and how many of us are planning
on seeing the boys of summer this season
now business of baseball is in trouble
and attendance is plummeting across the
league including here in the city yeah
sure is overall the league attendance is
down six and a half percent from last
year and who's leading the way it is the
Toronto Blue Jays Francis a 29% drop-off
in attendance over last year the team
seeing about 429 thousand fewer fans so
far you know the reason is obvious when
you look at the performance 16 teams
including the Jays have lots more games
than they've won players are striking
out more often than ever 22 and a half
percent of the time the league
please face for more strikeouts than
hits the cost of going to the game
continues to rise the average ticket in
the league is 77 bucks
the teams though is whether you got a
hole not suffering too much financially
thanks to a big TV deals but the the CEO
the owner the worried about the future
of the game with people just not going
the way they used to pants and beer
what's happening with beer so the
government is about to undergo a
makeover here with beer what are they
doing changing the audition don't worry
we still have our beer like federal
officials they're proposing changes
franchise Francis to the national beer
standards that would widen the number of
ingredients permitted in beer and would
also though force of those ingredients
to be listed in more detail brewers
would be able to use a fruit or for
example lavender or coriander would
still have the beverage classed as beer
suds would no longer need to be
categorized into certain types like ales
doubt or Porter instead they're
proposing limits on sugar content to
simplify the language around the use of
additives in an effort to define what
beer is and some say this is going to
spur on a lot of innovation in the
industry others though warned that the
detailed labeling may cost a lot of
smaller Brewers too much my and they put
them out of business
coriander lavender beer I don't know
I'll stick to my moles and get a tea and
I think all right thank you Richard